Walks a beat in the city light
Flashing blues under New York nights
But his heart's up north where the rivers run free
With a blonde haired beauty from April Country
He's got a bad dream and a thing for a laugh
Caught a glimpse of her smile
Now he's doing the math
From the Bronx to the Bush
Oh, he's thinking real deep
Paige, are you the one I've been missing in my sleep?
Paige, will you fall in love with me?
Fishin' rock for a badge and a bee
Bring the charm, you bring the fear
Made from a city spark, hunting love in the big ol' dark
So what do you say?
Let's rewrite destiny
Paige, will you fall in love with me?
He dreams of her boots in his uptown bed
Laughin' at the dumbass jokes he says
She's guttin' trout, he's eatin' steak
Somewhere in the middle they both take a break
He'd trade his night stick for a fishin' pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol
Oh Paige, don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Paige, will you fallin' right shotgun free?
We'll mix malls and ice with whiskey fried
City boy and wild Canadian bride
I'll keep the peace and keep it wild
Together we'll tame each other's styles
So what do you say?
Baby set me free
Page, will you fall in love with me?
Mean you kill like you clean house
I just wanna kiss that pretty mouth
You fish, you hunt, you drink like a king
Damn girl, you make my star and sing
Hey, will you fall in love? Let's blend our flags and play in a tree
I'll hold you close my heart
I'm just a cop with a country dream
A bonfire's near and a northern queen
Say the word girl, give me that key
Say
Basically I thought every per gay guy the b-
Well, I'm saying like I was like when I came back from taking a piss and I was like I'm getting a beer
They're like they're like oh, he shut it down because Mike porn bombed him I go
Oh, that was his final magic trick. I go well
Did he show his he showed his cock or he showed his ass and they're like oh he showed his ass
I go. Yeah, she's too afraid to show his dick
You don't see your ass to a gay person because we that's we like we like it even more than the dick
You're a bottom though, aren't you?
Oh, no, no, no, I mean, it's like I'm I always I know no offense. No offense
I don't like to be like penetrate. I want to be like I don't even like to penetrate
I just want to think I always I always thought you were a bottom. No offense
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You'll show your dick. You'll be backstage. We can have so many freak
off. I appreciate we don't want to see you. I'm trying to show you now.
He just pulled his ass out like you know. It's nice. I mean they're like they're
I mean, I don't know if you guys can hear me, but I think you go to sleep happy.
I don't even care if you can't hear me anymore.
Watch me sleep.
God, I'm attracted to Mike Schrukoff.
He's so cute.
And probably never work out.
He probably like fucking-
Another show, my cock and a porn bomb, then my ass, I got no ass, it's like, this is
what my ass looks like, you ready?
Right here.
Ready?
My ass looks like I got like that fucking ass dude. I got nothing dude. No junk in the truck
I mean, I've been out and I mean I had nothing to but it's all about how you like where am I
I'm not gonna embarrass myself, but I mean I'll just embarrass myself cheers bro. Happy birthday to me. Here's why is my camera?
Fuck
Don't know do you hear me? You might are you on your computer? Yeah. Well, I'll be back
I'll try you might or you might have to restart it or restart the driver. It's an average of the browser back
Yeah, reset the browser. That's probably not gonna work, but
Yeah, I got it. I got it. I got it back. Oh
Yeah, but your camera's still off
Hey, by the way
I mean, I don't have to live anymore.
I mean, I saw everything I want to see in this world.
I mean, it's like, I just want to, like,
mic stroke off to, like, give me a chance.
Now that he has, I really don't want it,
but I just wanted to know if he would, you know?
You thought, he said, show your ass,
but he's saying, show your ass.
Yeah, I said, show your ass.
I didn't mind.
I'm not even delete that stream. Yeah, I went to I want to go get a beer and take a piss and I came back and everything
Was shut down like what the fuck?
This is worlds of prudish. Oh
You can't even show that a man's back. I mean, I don't understand this world anymore. It's gonna be so sick
I mean, it's like it mean it. I'm sad. I
Again, I don't know why I'm on camera
The fuck you need to restart your computer and restart your drivers. Okay. I'll reserve my computer. Okay. Oh
Yeah, for five minutes. I got you, bro. I'm not gonna pull my asshole out
I mean, it's okay, but you just have to put it backstage for me
Shit Goddy
Where were you all night? Alex was on here. I figured Goddy would be here while Alex was fucking over here
You just creep in the chat
the comb-over has to go well jt when you turn your fucking camera on you faggot i'll tell you
how you can wear your hair bitch like fuck maybe your sister can go do your fucking hair for you
give a fuck nigga like i almost bought a ferrari but the bank wouldn't approve the loan
yeah because you're broke thank you goddy i appreciate it
I'll send you a very gift soon.
Gotti, it's my birthday today.
What the fuck?
Not tomorrow, not fucking payday.
My birthday's today.
Send me some money now, Gotti.
Gotti, do I get a gift?
Oh, hold on.
Gotti, I remember I said the World's Fair,
or something like that.
No, I knew that.
I knew Wizard of Oz was going to do the World Fair too,
but that was like 18 million units.
But that was like, it was 18 and 30s too.
Hey, why am I so drunk?
That's embarrassing. Okay, I was gonna read you the battles. How much how much will you try tonight?
Not enough here. Oh, here we go. There's a trackable
I hope Alex comes back I hope she does too. I'm sorry. I mean I say I'm sorry
I didn't know I said I killed the whole stream that killed the whole stream
I know I said can I see your abs Mike and then he pulled he bent over and showed a butt hole
I mean it's embarrassing for everybody, but it's okay Mike. I forgive you
I'm sorry. I used to pull my butt. I'm sorry. I'm not regretting my decisions. I just like pull your ass out
And I was like abs ass abs. They sound very similar. I
Want to see both of them?
I'm in love
That's gonna give you some love handles to hold on to gosh. I got a Hank Hill ass. What are you talking about?
That's why I said I was like I don't know what my cock to my ass like fuck it. I'm a porn boss
Yeah, let's see over the other world. Oh my god, this is hot
Oh my god guys. This is my this is my my show is arrived. This is my dream no time
I mean, I don't have any other thing.
I mean, I guess the show's done
because it's like, I've seen everything I want in my life.
I don't know, maybe Olivia or any more, right?
Hey, I got a gun.
Just come in, just get in bed with me
and we can sleep forever.
I got a gun with one bullet, bro.
We'll put it to one end and then we'll shoot
it here and here.
Okay, I'll be backstage to put anybody on if they want to,
but I'm just spoiling the mood.
You guys.
I hate these, but I've been.
This motherfucking
Fucking great god-looking motherfucker over here, dude. God damn, bro
Beards immaculate ah damn dude. I had a beard like that once I had a beard like I lose my shit comes in when it comes in
Takes about what I took you like nine months nine months. I'm just happy. I don't have me
Now I'm just sitting here all mute dude fucking looking at a bunch of fucking mimes
No, it's so good, um, I don't get haircuts. I don't get trims, so
Yeah, I'm I'm balding on top
I don't give a shit
Hey, guess what I fucking only had three haircuts in my entire life
Get the fuck out of here
I'm 50 fucking two
Don't believe you're 52. I can't hear anybody again. Just like that's out cuts in cuts out weird
52 oh
We don't have to shame anybody about anything. Do we?
We don't have the same about you. Hey, you don't have to shame about your age
You don't have to shame about how much light you have
Isn't it weird how people just want to fucking I don't just like
Critical weird and talk all this shit. Everybody wants to fucking have like a dig a dig a dig a dig a knife in the back
to twist a little harder
It's fucking weird
So wait Mike who's older you and your brother and I'm muted again
Eddie the twins the twins. Oh, I'll fix you. I'll fix you Mike
better
Mike
Hey guys, you know I'm a part-time I'm Batman
Mike how much for like it's recent with you and your brother at the same time. I'm just interested. I mean, I don't know
I can only hear you
For perfect. I don't want you to hear that. I'm just watching him babble and him look at his phone, but I can hear you
I'm gonna go man. I'm gonna go because I'm a little bit worked up right now. I'm in the wild
I'm LD lives Gunry Sergeant. Hey, I'm best job
Yeah, I hope my mic's not messing up everybody else's uh, I I got the crickets. I got the cicadas. I'm out here
And damn cicadas, dude. They loud bro. They've screech
It's uh, huh. It's a it's a constant static no matter what you're trying to do
Alex Alex said she'd be back in like 10 minutes
So I hope Sykes here to let her back up
It's kind of weird just down a couple dudes and I can't hear anything
Turn your volume look out. Yeah, I'm gonna turn this around
See where I'm looking looking at me
Look at this shit the stairs go up so far. I'm six two. This is my head
This is the dock put the I'm gonna go ahead and put the light
Well that fucks everything up for the camera doesn't it now. I can't see shit
Where the fuck is everyone the fuck? Hey, can you hear me? Yeah, I can hear you
So so look at this shit like I'm sick. I'm six two
Right, that's how low the that's how low the water is
Those steps are supposed to match with the dock. I know but you you dove into a pool
You dove into a pool before not a dog
No, that that wasn't a pool. That's that's a lake. Oh, it wasn't a pool. It was just a stair case leading into a
Open water
Yeah, just that's an open water lake out there. That's cool
That's the thing that we used to get the dog in and out
Okay
And this is the dock
Concrete and the concrete. I don't know what I know it's and and there's another dock over there
And if you look up, oh, maybe the light will work.
This is a boat drop up here.
You got to this side and of that side
and no stairs don't, man, no stairs don't even try.
And then you got these stairs,
the lake's down like at least six feet.
Oh, the water level, the water table we have.
of the
Okay, so you're by me. You're by the East Coast. I'm in Jersey. So
You go you go crabbing. Do you go crabbing off the dock?
You guys know I can't say I'm
Not much of a fisherman
Yeah, I've never gone fishing. I've only gone crabbing. I picked up some uh
Clams before
Well, I was out paddleboarding and whatnot. Yeah
But I'm not much of a fisherman
of the
I got to read you on my camera of my camera spot.
I was food service in the army.
92 golf.
So intractable.
What's up, brother?
So you said you're a military man, what branch?
Yeah, it was 92 golf in the army.
Food service.
I'm not too familiar with Army MOS.
I know like O3 is infantry, but...
Or not
O3 is Marine Corps 11 Bravo is a army
Yeah, I was I was food service
Yeah, I was 35 31. I was a motor transport operator. I
drove like a seven I drove like seven ton trucks and shit between like, you know
Forward operating bases and like satellite bases and shit when I was deployed how long
How long we in the army for?
from 2003 to 2009.
So you did more than four years?
Yeah, I did a re-enlistment.
Did you, well, your second enlistment got cut short.
Was it a medical or a general discharge?
No, my original was five years.
Okay.
And the window opened a year early.
So now I'm at four years. Stop loss. And they they kind of did that to me. What years? What year did you serve? What years?
2003 to 2009
so I did yes, I did 07 to 211 and
Did you did you deploy?
No, honestly, I did not you never you never served abroad
But I served in Korea twice
Okay, so you were actual active army you were in like National Guard or anything like that, you know, oh
No active all six years. Okay. Would you you got E3 E4?
I reached corporal. I went through the board
for promotions and I went through the
NCO Academy
Well, yeah, if you hit corporal you're an E4 like
in the Marine Corps well
The branches are different
Marine Corps, we've got private private first-class land score pool corporal, you know
The army it's weird. They got they got like private
specialist, you know fucking I'm not too sure about
well
That's cool. Oh, man. Thank you. Thank you for your service, man. Like I said, you know, I did I did four years, too
I got deployed twice
One time I went to one time. I went to Japan one time. I went to fucking Africa, you know, it's um,
It's different for everybody
Yeah, for sure
For sure, but I love I love talking to veterans because there's a lot of people like I know
the
It's honestly that shit that shit doesn't even so it's funny because like you know when you compare like so you were in the army
Right. I was in the Marine Corps when when you compare like the army to the Marine Corps like I feel like the Marine Corps
I just draw like stricter regulations like you can't wear your utilities outside the base
Right if you're if you're on libo or anything like you have to wear your civvies
You can't just wear your fucking mar path or anything right like you can't wear your fucking
Classes or bravos like fucking
So if you saw like a fucking guy
All face
Both you army men
How come the military career ended and you're not still like Marines?
How did you end up diving a swamp to fight alligators and you want a bad old sexy naked drinking beer?
what happened to me
I got my EAS. I got my end of active service and
I was tired of waking up at five o'clock in the morning for fucking formation. I was tired of not being able to smoke weed
I was tired of like
Yep, yep, if you're gonna be a soldier or anything in productive life you better wake up at 4 a.m
Beyond that highway at five and at work as early as they say
You gotta wake up at 3 a.m
I told the guy at work the other day that I was in the Marine Corps and literally I was walking out for a cigarette
And he went a 10 hut 2992 and I was like I literally stand at attention
I was like holy fuck like it like my PTSD just snapped in I was like I haven't stood attention in like fucking 15 years like
He was a staff sergeant he was a staff sergeant the guy that I was talking to in the Marine he went into the Marines
Oh, I'll these don't he tell me Marine. Yes. Yes
Wow, and you actually were a marine because if you were a marine you have a little diploma that says I'm a marine
I have I have a thing called an honorable discharge. Yeah
All right
All right, so you cooked ham at least this guy made
marine
What the fuck did you do on trackable you cooked ham in korea?
Or japan? Well, what were you cooking in my boy?
Hey, I mean we all did our things
How the fuck did they let you in the army?
You didn't put them to sleep
Like why do you want to be a soldier like a muntrakable?
Like how did you make it?
That's what I want to know and then you end up so you went across these
questions
It's a miracle you even made it through the process
Which service were you in sir?
And what people I'm not military like you you
My boy my yeah, I'm here, bro
Who's talking?
Me me. I'm talking who you don't have a you don't you don't have a combat
You don't have any combat action ribbons at all. No, no, I'm just civilian
I'm where PD any schmuck and began with PD. You guys are soldiers. You actually joined
That's a whole day from
It is true
You can't graduate high school and join the NYP day
Are you telling me you graduated high school and join the NYP day because when I got out of the Marine Corps I joined the fire department
Okay
Okay, so so did you go to college for criminal justice or anything like that?
Like yeah, St. John St. John Jay in the city my boy
Yeah, my my best friend my best friend from the Marine Corps. He went to pace
It's a good one too. So why are you off tracking though? Why are you going?
I mean you want to want to be a cop. What do you want? What am I my step my stepbrother when he got out of the Marine Corps?
He he became a cop. He's still a cop. He's a sergeant detective. He does
Homicides and stuff where where in Jersey. I don't want to say where but um
He does he's a sergeant detective now when he does the vehicle homicides like vehicle fatalities and stuff like traffic accidents and stuff
It's amazing, bro
Well, I mean he was a patrolman. He was a patrolman for like six years before he got to detectives
So you have to you have to be
You become a rookie and if you do your thing you get promoted fast if you're some loser you you'll never get promoted
Depends what you want
Right. Others want to be Sergeant Lieutenant. Most of the cops don't want that.
They, they, they, they just want the 20 years to mention the thing, it depends bro. Everyone's so different in that sense.
There's no such thing as a Sergeant Lieutenant.
No, no sergeant and lieutenant. You have to take a time. Yeah, you become detective first grade second grade third grade
Sergeant, right? Then you're running a squad. So now when you become a
You're actually you're actually overlooking for losers. So for rookie dickheads under you
Officers, you're running them. They give you a little team to run if you can do that good
Lieutenant test and then you're the boss
When you're a lieutenant with a white shirt, you're their boss. You have to listen to anything
That's respect then it's captain and chief
I never I never wanted to be a cop. I never wanted to be a cop my brother
My brother when he got on the Marine Corps my step-brother
Yeah, I always want to be blown. Oh, I never I never I've been the fire department
I was like man
Everyone when the fire department shows up there fucking clapping and cheering five department
It's actually more amazing than the cops. I think in a way man. Don't that's insane
I grew up in New York man the FDNY. I mean, they're great, but
when I lived out when I got to the Marine Corps
when I was in Vegas, those people were kings, man.
Vegas has the fucking one of the toughest fire departments
in the world.
They literally have not lost a person in like a structure fire
since like the 80s when I was trying to join them.
Since then, they're so insane.
They're so out of control brain.
I didn't take the civil service.
I was waiting for the civil service.
But FDNY, like they're all brain.
It's weird.
Well, it's New York's bravest. Yeah, I mean fucking but
The actual fire department in Vegas though, even though they've got high rises and a lot of structure fires and stuff like that
It's like
They have not lost a person in a structure fire since like the 80s, but you got a control
You're on a little ladder from a truck with 200 pounds of gear
You know trying to save people from burning fire this got the Scott packs the fucking
Sawzalls and whatever the fuck you're
When I was in the fire department, I mean, I'll show you my fucking ID
I'll show you my fucking homeland security ID
I was writ a rapid intervention team alpha if a fucking if a firefighter pulled their
Wow, holy shit
Alex Alex, what would you rather date a cop or a firefighter?
Firefighter, there you go. That hurts. That hurts. I would know and I'll tell you why because a firefighter if I if something
Horrible look like the number one the firefighter would find me
That's number one because they're natural hunters. They can go through the smoke through all of that. They know what they're doing
The cop it's more about logistics the firefighter is more about survival
Correct something about fire fighters separates them
Well, the firefighter look I I you call them you call them you call them when you're in need of help
The same thing with the fire this isn't the police department, but from the police department
They target actually but the fire fighters to stay more like pure and more like go nation like confident
Like they don't need a gun. They just come to help you my like the power
My dad's on my family
My grandmother and they've all passed away, but my grandmother, she was one of the first African American nurses in New York City.
Her name is Alice. Okay, Alice, Alice mayors. And she actually, she was kind of like a savant strangely from Pittsburgh.
when it came to her cerebral capacity she had like a scholarship to go to New York
and she integrated with within my um fathers which was her family but my grandfather's family
and he was a police officer that's how they met in the ER unit believe it or not.
But he was a police officer, he wound up getting in trouble because there was some corruption and he took the fall for it, but she was one of the first African American legitimate nurses in New York City.
So that's like history, like American history.
Like, we're gonna look it up.
Alice Mayors, Alice Mayors.
That's part of the reason my name is Alexandra,
because initially my dad wanted my name
to be Alice after his mom,
but my mom didn't agree with it,
so they settled on Alexandra.
That's so funny, because my parents didn't,
my mom wanted my name to be something
and my dad didn't agree with it.
that's the thing but my grandfather's on my dad's side on the grandfather's side of the family
they were marines they they were some of the first black marines in the united states of america
back then back then the military used to be segregated it was
And my grandfather, part of the reason that my grandfather lost his position in NYPD at the time had to do with corruption, him being blamed for something that he should not have been blamed for, but because he was a man of color.
And honestly, barely a man of color when you really, if you were to look at photographs.
that they were able to
In the Hamptons Hamptons detective, right? And they fired her because of that
No, there's a lot of corruption
It's called that's not cool
You know what i'm saying? That's just still goes on
It's everywhere. It's it's not unfortunately. Unfortunately. Yes. It does still go on
But it's not and they don't record it like
Correct, the body camera changed the whole game, but the higher-up can get around it.
They can get around it.
L.A. is a woman, is a lesbian woman, and she's never even been like a firefighter.
She was always like a fucking, uh, like a, like a clerk.
And now she's the fucking chief of fire, uh, fire department in L.A.
Why she's not the best I love when I see that when I see woman running like police departments
Like I think in LA though the chief of police is a lady
How crazy
But she earned it she earned it she's been on the floor for like 30 years worked her way up and earned it
But that's the best when I see shit like that when things go wrong typically people send their
Bring their children to school
It's the mind that matters not the decos of vagina. You understand
Who you live the job to?
as the la police chief just because we have a dick or she has a pussy no you're gonna join
their mind and talk please go ahead baby go please what i'm gonna say is that what typically happens
with my younger. And I call them nieces, but they're not my
siblings, children, but my cousin's children. But I still call
them all nieces and nephews. We all send them to school. They
become doctors or attorneys, one of the two. So even if like, I
don't worry about certain things, because I have amazing
attorneys in my family to where something happens. I'm safe.
because I don't pay for I pay for the friggin
you can't let me Alex are you have are you have Jewish Alex
you think they'll talk to you if you have a $600 dollar an hour attorney
my last name is mayors y'all know my last name my legal last name is mayors
isn't it ain't made up some people pronounce it Myers but no I can stop a
Christian but it's closely related
And I don't disagree with a lot of things. Oh, I love the song you played before with psyche
You were exercising the demon the prayer of David's own. He's resistant. I'm trying
Yeah, the demon had a motherfucker. He's a devil
with stupid
Yeah, he's the devil and he needs you to exercise the demon out of his head. I'm a reminder
of some things
It's either you or me. I don't want to do it, baby. You you have a nice
Maybe you have a brother do up with him. I don't have an iron face
I don't want to put him to that the guys been through so much already
Don't don't don't bring up things that are gonna mess it up the queen stop it
Stop it queen. Stop it
McQueen
So when so when's the fashion show gonna be?
We want it, baby
You see it's like this fashion show. Do you know LD? Do you know LD well? Not very well. Yeah, LD is awesome. What?
but I knew probably I knew when we do with doogaloo's
I met her like five years ago, dude. I did not meet you five years ago. You know, I know I'm kidding
I don't know him better than you but I know LD LD 15
Protect his identity because he's undercover
LD I start off for him
I like those things.
Where's, where's Psych?
Well, I understand Spanish.
He's walking up McDonald's.
I was asking Alex if he speaks Spanish.
Oh, oh.
He would get a really good enlistment, not enlistment bonus,
but wherever they call it.
In the ice, if he speaks Spanish, like...
Yeah, let's find out heaven
He's laying on the floor by the way, he's on the deck. He's laying on the floor
Are you in the Navy is this a
That's what I'm saying. If I'm
on the deck, McQueen, that's
what are you doing there? Are
you burglarizing that house?
Is this door a porthole? This
He does this every year. He goes to this house. We don't know who owns it and he goes
is a porthole.
It's weird house. It is his house. It's his house. Obviously. It's his house. Yeah, somebody's mommy his wife
Maybe his
No, it's my they would not let some sasquatch take on their deck
Diving into a lake if it wasn't related to him. So is this house
What do you know? Do you know that it's LT's birthday?
That's important. You understand that.
Yeah, it's my birthday today.
I'm not gonna sing Happy Birthday to him. I'm gonna sing it to girl.
I said Happy Birthday, LT. Many, many blessings.
Many years trying to make it to 100 years old. That's my mission.
I'm gonna make it to 100. I don't go.
You're gonna make it to like 200.
Yeah, exactly. The longer I'm gonna keep it going till I can.
Don't give a fuck. I'm gonna keep it going to the more to the very end, bro
I gotta do 120 130. I gotta have a walker. Whatever. I'm gonna run this shit into the ground
Every second that God gives me I'm not gonna give up at 80 90 fuck that
I'm gonna keep it going
What are you
When I was a little kid that I was gonna live a very long life. I remember this at three four five years old
Just having some feeling now that I think about like reincarnation and karma and all that thing
Maybe I lived a life right before I was born because why would a three four-year-old have this?
Deep feeling he's gonna live to be a very very old man. I always had
Okay
so maybe hold on check this out so maybe the life before me every incarnation is real
some very old man died and then i was born took his spirit and i feel his spirit like i'm gonna live
to nine years i mean either that or i'm crazy because i i was feeling this before i knew
Yeah, I was a little kid in Colombia, and I always had this feeling like I'm gonna live till I'm like 900 years old
I didn't know why I felt that way, but I always had it in me like it was a hundred percent guaranteed
And I get older and older and I'm like life is short. You can die at 50, right? Oh life comes in cancer
This that but when I was three or four I felt it completely natural. So then I started investigating
And then people say reincarnation and all this shit and blah, blah, blah, blah.
So maybe my only logical answer for me to be that young, four years old,
and feel that I'm going to live to 900 years old without anyone talking to me.
No one like laid me in bed and was like, you're going to live to 900 years old.
Like it was just in me.
It was just a feeling I had from a little kid.
So I'm assuming that an energy took over me
That's what reincarnation does right someone dies and that energy goes into someone else and it gets reborn
And you do a new life. So I think whoever was my past life was a
Was a very old man
passing his energy
The older than me
Well, I'll explain me. Am I crazy? Wait, wait, wait, Alexander. Let let L. D. Alexander. Can you get it?
Carnation, right? Like a traditional
Indian like
No, no, but why at a young age?
I commit a lot of bad acts. I'm gonna come back as a slug, right? I'm gonna come back as a slug
Yeah, I have to do is a slug to move my way back up the food chain
And McQueen your volume is so high like like do you have it on the highest level like let's turn it down a little bit
Just we can still hear you, but you have it on like max to where nobody else can talk
I'm just saying if you're a piece of shit and you're reborn
You're gonna be reincarnate as a slug or a worm or whatever what you've done
To move your way back up the story like a human
Look at Alexander was sexy. Don't tell me to lower my mic, baby
But I want to hear everybody talk and Alexander, you know, I love you, but you
all right i'll turn it down you know we we're still listening now with me i always thought
i was i would live to be about close to two hundred i was shocked when my dad died as to me
my dad died early in my opinion okay how old was he how old was he
Close to 80 but in his late 70s. I always thought he was gonna be like
He was old when I had you he was old when he had you yeah, both my yeah, my parents had and I was the first
They have me later in their life. Your mother was young. I assume your mother was young much
No, my mom my mom is pretty. She's older
really that's why I thought my doubt was gonna be around longer because until
the cancer hit him your mom died first no my mom's still alive yeah my mom is
alive and she's not in like that I talked to her every other day of course
all right yeah
is that what's up I thought that my dad always seemed more um
well like jubilant more energetic but he burnt out because he came over and clean and cook for you
Alex no I know when if you come over with like me we're all crazy in our family but um
no when I visit her I clean and I cook for her I don't have anybody I clean and cook for myself
And I'm a I'm a neat freak actually, but oh you sound like the person I need to move into this house because I'm not a neat freak
How could you leave this beer can
My friends
do not like me because I cleaned their houses is ridiculous. Yeah, I would hate that. Oh my
god, that's the plenty of shit.
That's the point. But you know what? I do the same. I do
Alex as soon as I walk into someone's house if it's too messy, I start picking shit up
Putting in the garbage. I take out the garbage
And they're like, yo, I didn't invite you to clean my house. I'm like, I can't be here like this, bro
I like oh my god. Your garbage is full. What the fuck? I'll be right back. I think that shit out
I'm horrible. I'm horrible. Because if people get back
any time I visit family, you can't take out your garbage. It's
full motherfucker. I mean, look, I'll tell you when I met psych,
if he would have let me in this house, I would have cleaned
the whole damn thing. But it was that's how I am. That's me.
But I was right. Exactly. That's why I can't visit psych. I'll
go crazy. I'll dine. He's trying to clean all that shit up.
My dad was always super duper messy, but my mom was super duper OCD and I heard your dad was gay. Is that true?
Obviously, I exist so he had to have been by all right, so he won't get
after he had you.
Why are you going to bring that up like what's that matter?
Because I don't know.
I'd rather talk about that than throwing that garbage.
So hold on.
So the guy had you with the mom.
Hold on Alex.
Don't don't don't run away.
Don't over talk me.
and turn your volume down if you really want to talk about it.
You have it as loud as I do, baby, so relax.
No, not really, I don't.
Well, you hear your dad passed away from cancer, right?
Yes, he did.
So wait, hold on.
I need answers, though.
Brain?
Why would you call Psyche on F4?
No, it's from the lungs, the heart, to the, you know, the
the paper is to you know, all
your mids. Yeah, I almost died
yesterday. I swear to God, I was
close in the street. I wasn't
checking in a bus.
flew by at like a hundred miles an hour it almost clipped my nose
Yeah, this is very personal this is very personal questions like
Anyone on here like no, all right
everything central in the he had a heart issue. I was with him through the heart.
But how many cocks did he suck before the heart issue?
I don't want to be on this panel. I'm how many.
So hold on. You can hear her.
Wait, what? What?
She said the man is gay. I was being he's a cock suck up and sucked in the
way she left. Oh, you guys are crazy.
That's crazy
Respectful, thank you fuck that this was back. Well, I'm loving I'd love to be a cop and be so disrespectful
Bro, I'm doing her a favor. She needs to face this shit
No, it's not gonna be McQueen. It's gonna be somebody else later. It's gonna hurt even more. You're talking about
I'm giving her a tough game
The one they come front there in real life about this shit
McQueen and laugh at all. Yeah, okay. I'm helping her
So anyway, Alex get back up. You how many takes did you that suck before whatever happened to him?
psyche sucks a cock
Everyone sucks cock. I'm up
What happened? No can do eat my boy. It's me and Santa Claus
Oh, great one. Did I just see the back chat Alex say get Alex off the panel?
That's hilarious
Chief long done equal
Chief long done. I'll tell you what this is
This is my queen fucking shit up. That's what this is
All right, there's only one Alex and one Alex in this town.
It's no room for two Alex's, my babes.
So yeah, I love you on trackable.
Look at that little nose, little bleh.
Look at him, nice hair.
All right, my babes.
Think that is, hit the link.
If I see no hair, I don't know what to do, my boy.
You can get it to pay you can like girl put season in this stuff to do you can get like an implant of hair
Well, you don't have that much money. That's like 20 grand for fake hair
This hair plugs. I had a bald loser that friend of mine that did it, but he was rich
Yeah
It like fucking college. He done loser one crazy and he fucking all of a sudden
He just came in with new hair one day
But his dad on one of the biggest our churchional companies in New York, you know, he had loot for the fake hair my babes
My dad blessed me with a poor head of hair. Yeah, mine too mumbo chief London
That that that becomes a question in life is like
There you go
Untrackable take it from here, bro. Please put us to bed tells us story. You got it
Well, would you would you rather be natural and have people hate you for that?
Or would you rather waste a bunch of money and have a failure of a surgery and have people hate you for that?
It depends how like a vein you are like, uh, there's a sin vanity vanity when you look in the mirror a day and like, you know, it's called vanity. That's a sin.
Yeah, so I am who I am.
And I know, bro. That's why I love you, dick. You have no vanity in you. You're special. I get it. So you don't have to explain it to me, bro. Trust me. I see right through everything.
But if you want to get down to business, yeah, it's called vanity and some people are so
Vain and so caught up in their looks that you know everything. Oh
On travel don't give a fuck
Naked in the fucking lake. I mean here I am. I don't pay the garage. What?
Everyone's like
You don't gotta chop it on my throat asshole
to look at this, I put my beard to the side, I got a tan line
from my beard
you look like a tomato actually, you've been tanning, how are you, look at you
I got a tan
my beard was
it's crazy
it's a supermodel bro
some people are supermodels without even trying
that's your gift
Yeah, it's like, you know, you know, some some guys just gotta like that, bro
I'd like to think I'm one of those but I don't know, you know, but you're definitely one of those dick
Some guys just got like that. It doesn't matter. They could wear fucking
Whatever they just hot
They just got it. That's it
A lot of people got to try hard
You just roll out of bed like boom supermodel doesn't matter. What the fuck you do?
Well, is it that is it that how?
People hate you my boy. I'm beat. It's another saying out here
Do you get the say this this is how it works?
They get normal dudes to model underwear
because
Because because it's underwear
But they get hot chicks to model special underwear so that way dudes will buy their chicks
That's special underwear. You see how it works
They're sick and grown how they like try to put a seed in your mind. What a person should look like a
Man should look like this a woman should look like this. That's crazy
They're trying to break your mind and fuck a lot of up
Like nobody should look like anything you look away like what you look like. Yes, the media and the magazines have their little
You know model shit
Victoria's Secret they should be this that this that but that's all bullshit if you feed into that you're far
You understand you're never gonna find love you're gonna be chasing a fucking magazine cover your whole life
And and and you are what you do?
So
You're gonna look a certain way if you if you do certain things
But look like how you want it depends. What's inside right? You can be it though
You can be some six three dark laundry and blue hair blue. I and be the biggest loser
Like you don't know nothing or you can be whatever you want
Don't be into shit and at the end of the day who you're laying in bed with when the lights go off
That's what matters, right? It's dark. It's you and them
It's not some supermodel and you cuz he's got the fucking buns of ass and 10
Nickelback's like hello
That's what fucks a life man of time this this commercial shit
Oh, yeah, I'm people what they need to love. That's basically what they do
Like this is what a man is this is what a woman should be and
Out there to get on a bus and they're like when like they just prefer fucks them on them
Hey, everything that they sell is something that you won't and you'll never get it through a dollar
Every single thing that they sell to you
There's something you want. All right, that they don't give a fuck about they just want you to want it
It's not like they want it. They're like look what this loser wants like let's just sell it to him
And they just collect the money and keep growing
That this this smell will attract women or that's insane
Yeah, that's so great this smell
How about you attract the girl bro because the bitch likes you like what the fuck this mouth?
Yeah, no, I'm not I'm not saying cologne doesn't work because it does man. It's ready guy
I love cool water. I had bitches on my dick of cologne. So it's true
But that's not the final thing bro if you can't get a girl without the cologne you don't deserve the girl
No, it's about the it's about the long term
Cuz you you don't wash your ass, but you sprayed yourself when you got off work
That's called a Puerto Rican bath my boy
That's a Puerto Rican bath
Yeah, and they just think even worse. That's just smells like how like you didn't take a shower
You don't ever not shower and spray cologne to try to cover it. That's a Puerto Rican bath
Yeah, so
But yeah, so same thing look the long-term be like oh, I can see you know
I I could get the hair plugs and have my shit looking all nice and
and then the girl gets with me because I got you know nice hair and
She wants her jeans to be nice too. Yeah, but you could be bold and I have a Porsche and the girl get with you
Like you know like what is she really like? Who what is she? She doesn't even know you like
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Three months, you know the bitch you marry that means the pussy
You know what that means that you're such a loser. You haven't got pussy your whole life
This bitch spread her legs for three months daily and you marry her and now she owns half your shit
Like there's a lot of losers out there like that
That they don't get pussy and once one bitch spreads it 24 seven for them. They'll fall for it
That's crazy
I heard about I heard about these seminars where it's like
It's damn near twenty thousand dollars for a three-day weekend. Oh my god
$20,000
Listen, they're gonna they're gonna turn you into a man. They're gonna put you through
So much training in three days
And you're going to pay $20,000 for this bullshit.
It's like, that's exactly what we got paid to do.
Like, I got $2,000 a month to go through those.
I didn't have to pay a goddamn thing.
All I had to do is say, yes, pay me.
But they paid $20,000, like, hey, make me a man over three days because I am so retarded.
Make me a man over three days. He's 20 grand. What? That's crazy.
No, the rest of us.
But he made me a man. So, the rest of us pay me and make me a man.
20 grand.
I'll make you a man dig. Join the army. Go cook like on track of one Korea
At least you went to bull camp, you know
Okay, you paid 20 grand and
You know
Somebody tortured you for three days
Whereas I got paid for six years and I tortured myself for six years
That there were there was no test. I could not pass you understand that right? Yeah
Correct, your mind won't let you fail. You just couldn't that was out of the equation
You're not passing. I get it. I'm the same way like once my mind focus
I was not allowed to fail
Exactly you won't let yourself a lot and once you do that the universe will shift into that purpose with you bro.
Once the mind becomes not strong it just like takes hold of the universe and it will shift it like if you don't want to shift it for me i want to shift it for you motherfucker.
Once that mentality goes into place.
It can be stopped.
It can't be stopped on and the universe will help you and go with it
It's about kind of like I've done it multiple times
It's kind of like talking to you at 3 a.m.
Yeah
Does Alex win
Where's the money coming from
Because if our money is equal then
Alex will never beat me
Don't know what you're talking about money, but I got out of the bathroom bro. Give me two minutes
That's okay handy business
Thank you. I'll be right back. I literally gotta go take a leak man. I'm a troll
Yeah, you know you see what I mean?
You can't hold his water. He has no decorum
Oh, you were just to this or just to that
There's only two of us up here and all of a sudden you got to go to the bathroom
but this isn't about me and you it's about fucking people up that that actually deserve it
because they can't spend the time they can't say left right i'm just saying but i'll spend the
time with you when i have it to give doesn't hurt my feeling i'm back i'm back buddy you're good
of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of
If you had to make a whole scene of it like it's like hey, look at me. I'm taking a piss break
What do you want me disrespectful and just mute and then you're gonna be like Alex are you there Alex and leave you alone?
For two minutes, so I tell you bro. I'm going to the bathroom
So I don't answer
That's because I'm in the bathroom. So I do it
I don't even know why I should just not give a fuck what I gotta tell you when but I don't respect
Because it happens sometimes
I'll just mute up and go to the bathroom and I hope people like Alex
Answered and they're talking to me. I'm in the bathroom like fuck. So I like to announce it now
Like I'm going to bathroom two minutes from me. I
Know this is not my job, but I deal with that at the job all the time
the
day of
It doesn't matter what an asshole you are because now no I did tell you and I come back and you're making fun of me
They go Alex you had to make a thing out of it. So I can't win with you
Right if I tell you I made a thing out of it. If I don't tell you I'm an asshole
So which one is a poverty one?
Oh, you don't tell you
Because that's exactly what happened dick. You just said oh, you had to tell me when P
Huh? Yeah, you know that one
Hey, I'm not
You said it you you will be for that me because I told you and then you're beefing because I didn't tell you
And they told me a story about someone not telling you
So you're basically crazy. I just caught you in a crazy lie
And now I know once again
Then you're out of your fucking mind dickhead
So don't tell me so next time. I'm not gonna tell you
I'll just let you talk by yourself and question where I am
Because either way, you know, it doesn't matter with you, right? Tell them or don't tell them your fuck
Well, if you know them you're making a thing about it if you don't tell them
He's gonna tell your boss like you didn't tell me so how do you win with your stupid beard as?
well in in that case you should probably just mute up and
Let me no, I'm gonna mute. I gotta go to the bathroom again. Actually. I didn't tinkle all the way
Let's see what you talk now, what have you done. Let's see what happens
Yeah, go ahead mute up. I did a minute. Yeah
That's what that's what you should I'm muted. I'm muted up talk shit. Go ahead
Not muted it up. What are you talking? I am muted. I'm I'm muting just to tell you I'm muted, but I'm muted
Well, then get me you're here. All right. I'm gonna meet up right now done
Don't don't say my name though because then I got on mute
it so this uh...
I'm muted, I am
I'm muted
he doesn't know when to shut up
I'm not gonna say any names though
I'm muted as though
but there were these moments
when it's like hey
you made a good point
yeah exactly
they can
I thought you were muted
shut up
I am muted. So whose house are you burglarizing every year? Why do you go to that house and
die and wrestle alligators in their backyard pond?
Who is that? Is that your grandfather?
Your mama?
I'm training for your house, Alex.
Is there a Airbnb? You go every year with your...
I'm trading your family. I'm trading them for your house
Interesting interest. All right. Okay. I know you can't afford water. So
Yeah, yeah, water stop to find the targets. You got a baby box
For the water. Oh, yeah, so
So I had jet ski once it caused me a fortune. Yeah, just to put it in water is a nightmare
and
So I have to train well, I created my BMW in today for a Porsche. I got a Porsche, bro
Metallic blue. Yeah, it's the best thing on earth. I'm having a midlife crisis
Yeah, I was eyeballing this baby for a while and
You got a 1986 Porsche
And you wish you were
No, twin turbo and it's a convertible
On top of it
You got any crazy, bro. I don't know how much time I got on this world, you know, fuck that
You know, you know how crazy I'm on track of all I want they had a white Ferrari
but I wanted the Ferrari dickhead and the bank wouldn't approve it
The bank wouldn't approve the loan for the Ferrari
That's how much you whoever has a Ferrari shout out to them because you need a lot of money
To get a fucking Ferrari bro
The bank wouldn't approve it. They only approve the Porsche
I was pissed. It was a white Ferrari white my boy like like Miami Vice
I
Approving 110 grand the fuck out of here. We just stupid 40 grand down
We're not doing it. My boy. My credit wasn't good enough for the Ferrari
They they were like well approving for the Porsche 80 grand
So you put half down 40 grand. Well, well, you know 40 grand will approve you want the Ferrari a hundred twenty grand
We're 40 grand. We're not approving a hundred grand credit. I was pissed, man
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
I'm not going to say you pay for work. You don't have to take my word for it
Well, I'll show you a picture of it. Hold on. Let me see if I can upload on the avatar. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on my boy
No, that doesn't work for me
Well, this is it. Take you you take it or leave it. What do you want me to do?
There it is. Okay. This is it. This is it. This is it. This is it. I know you ask for it
Look at it full screen McQueen. That's my new baby
that's my new baby
up bro it doesn't work like that, I know New York has plates
9-11 twin turbo my boy
but the same way I can go live in the lake you can go live
what? what up bro
that's my new car my boy
twin turbo 9-11
but you can't do that
of the
Can you 80 grand 80 grand? It's not brand new
The brand new ones are a hundred ten hundred twenty. So, you know, I'm not that much of a big tool
But the Ferrari I didn't get a proof of the Ferrari
But that's actually good because that would put a lot of eyeballs on me. Hey, fuck your car. Can you swim?
100% I can swim I'm a fish, bro
I can't can you prove can you prove it? Can you prove it?
I don't know me means the water one day me in the beach. I'll I'll swim you any day of the week, bro
Any day of the week I'll swim you on the water. I can hold my breath for five minutes stick head
You can't hold your breath. You smoke cigarettes loser. I don't I win right off the bat on that
to the
Look, you eat the fucking
They look like Swiss cheese. That's how look he's smoking as we speak those cigarettes have touched these lungs in
20-30 years
You think you're gonna outlast me. I will fucking knock you out in two seconds
I'll swim you anything you're gonna be huffing and puffing my friend in a minute
You're gonna be dying the fuck up man
the fuck suck on that cigarette again go ahead boy suck on the cigarette again for me do it
suck on that cancer steak i will knock you out brother i can jog seven miles and swim four
miles a triathlon king bro this little dives in a lisma grandma's lake and the fucking jumps
And you think you're gonna outlast a man like me
Where you buck to eat where your buck tooth teeth my peeps
Like you buck tooth boy
All the top buck tooth on the bottom hiding his face with his beard
Look at him coma
Yeah, I'm gonna say I got a Polish asshole
Gotta pause while you're on some your bias. Look at him teeth. Yeah, bucktooth. Look at you. No
Look at that gap between those teeth
And you got gap teeth I have a Porsche 911 twin turbo and you got gap teeth
What does that say for you on charcoal? What did you make at yourself in life?
you suck it on cancer steaks, take another motherfucking cigarette, take another cigarette, my boy
suck on that cigarette, suck on that cigarette, suck it, suck it, I know it's in your hand, you're dying to do it
don't hold back now pussy, take another, swagger that's sake
come on, look he's trying to hold it back
it's a brand new cigarette, it wasn't even like down to the, you know, the bottom
He's holding a cigarette in his hand right now and I want him to take a pull of it because I'm calling him out.
So you got the stupid beer and cancer sticks and you think you're going to outstrain McQueen.
Where did that dumb retarded like thought come in your mind, my boy?
Where the fuck in your brain you thought you can do anything better than McQueen?
You've been sucking on cancer sticks for decades.
that's that's that's a beautiful sentiment and I'm gonna keep on smokin and you and you're gonna keep on losing to me
well I'm just saying that
you hold on do you have to both say it's gonna be you
cause it's not gonna be you dickhead
so don't be that delusional moron
come on man
I jog 7 miles a day I don't touch cigarettes
I am in perfect shape
you're an old man sucking cancer sticks
alcohol who's gonna win that fight
you're in perfect shape
So I would break it to you, bro. It's not gonna be you
You're in perfect shape
You you are in perfect shape
You see how excited I am because I I would fuck you up in a heartbeat. Did you kick him or did he?
Lose himself. It's okay
330 here on the East Coast
Some of us are still swimming
Smoking or not smoking drinking or not drinking. It's not a competition like that
And until it is but you got to show up to grow up complainers never win
Like oh, you know, you're a problem. I can't deal with you. So so what do you do?
You put somebody down and all that it's like well
Come to my neck of the woods and put me down and it never happens. It's okay
It's a I don't come out here with these bugs
for no reason
I don't dive into the darkness for no reason.
I don't have free love for each and every one of you
for no reason, but for somebody that finds a way
to hate everybody and say, I'm better than you.
It's like, hey, Bill, that's all fine and good.
Don't you shit, you can get it out.
I think this is therapy for some people.
It's like, just say what you gotta say.
You'll win, you'll win today.
the loudmouth contest. I don't know why I'm up here by myself either.
But it is all fun and games. Time spent together. A bunch of willing participants.
And if somebody wants to talk mad shit, that's fine. If somebody has something to say that's
the same shit or even understanding what others are going through and so if that's what it's about and it's like
That's what it's about. I don't stick around for people's personal bullshit
But but if you want to have fun, I can have fun
Alex is in the back chat calling me a pussy pussy pussy pussy pussy. I mean I
Got your pussy right here, brother. I do shit on camera all the time
And, uh, more or less to entertain the people, you, you, from what we've seen, you won't do anything to prove yourself, you know, to us anyway, you know, one for one.
And that's fine.
No, no judgment.
I still respect you.
I still love you.
But you talk shit.
You get hit.
I don't I don't have to hit you everybody down there in the comment section is gonna be like hey
One dude's doing one thing and another dude's talking a whole bunch of shit
You you see this right
That's how it goes. I'm not worried about a dag on thing
Not worried about somebody calling me a pussy. I'm not worried about a challenge
No, not worried about it
Because in real life, I'm never gonna meet none of y'all.
Alex isn't gonna come from New York down here
to the water I'm in, at least while I'm here
for the next week, it's just not gonna happen.
And that's fine.
And my family's not gonna hold the phone
while I prove a point.
And that's fine too.
Because where's your family?
They're not holding your phone either.
Why you prove a point.
It's just not gonna happen. It's okay boys being boys
But as men we do this shit every single fucking day every single fucking day and I wish the best for each and every one
Whoever you are
However, you live your life
Get it enjoy it teach the next generation. That's really all you got
Competitions are fun. No, all they really do is give others something to look at
If they can't, if they can't see you do something while I spend time with my family,
you're just this dude that exists, talks mad shit. Good luck. Good luck with that life. Good luck with that life.